http://norfolkdailynews.com/site/privacy.html

Home
Norfolkdailynews.com is connected to the Norfolk Daily News newspaper located in Norfolk, Nebraska and owned by Huse Publishing. Internet Web sites exist to allow for and promote interaction. In that interaction, site visitors may provide information either anonymously or purposely about themselves, either statistically or personally. Norfolkdailynews.com is such a site.We understand that privacy is very important to our site visitors. We want to make sure that you understand why we collect certain information, how we use it, and how we protect it. We want our guests to feel confident that their personal information is handled with great care at Norfolkdailynews.com.I. Information That We CollectGeneral statistical information:Visits to Norfolkdailynews.com are monitored for the accumulation of statistical information, including such things as the number of visits to the site, the pages people visit, which domains the visitors come from and the browsers people use to visit the site.This statistical information is important to allow us to evaluate the effectiveness of the services we provide, to monitor our site performance and to make it easier for visitors to use the site.These statistics are anonymousUnless you tell us, through registration or communicating with us in some other way, we do not know who you are.What about personal information I give to Norfolkdailynews.com?If you communicate with Norfolkdailynews.com or register for any services on the site, we may collect the following information about you:· E-mail address· Name, address and telephone number· Financial information· Other demographic information you might volunteer, such as education or income levels, marital status, number of children in your home, hobbies or other personal interests· Other information to be determined in the futureYou may wonder why you would want to share personal information with Norfolkdailynews.com. The more information you volunteer, the better able we are to understand who our users are and the better able we are to improve and customize our site for you. Once you register on our site for any reason, you no longer are anonymous to Norfolkdailynews.com.In addition to information obtained through registration, Norfolkdailynews.com obtains personal information about you when you make a purchase. That information may include, but not be limited to, your name, address, e-mail address and what you have purchased.From time to time, Norfolkdailynews.com will conduct surveys on its site for research purposes. When you participate in a survey, the information you provide about yourself and the responses to the questions will be collected by Norfolkdailynews.com.If you contact Norfolkdailynews.com, we may keep a record of your identity and your correspondence.Norfolkdailynews.com also tracks and collects your computer's IP address to help with system administration and to compile information about traffic patterns on the site. Your computer IP address identifies your computer and the network or Internet service provider to which your computer is connected.What information is covered by this privacy policy? What isn't?All personal information you provide directly to Norfolkdailynews.com is covered under this privacy policy. This information may include but not be limited to your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card and other financial information, and other personally identifying information.Information that you might post on a story comment, guestbook, or forum is not protected under this privacy policy. Information posted in any of these public areas is not considered confidential communication. Norfolkdailynews.com has the right but not the obligation to monitor the content of its bulletin boards, story comments, guestbooks, forms, and forums to determine compliance with Norfolkdailynews.com policies and any other operating rules established for Norfolkdailynews.com. Norfolkdailynews.com shall have the right in its sole discretion, and without prior notice, to edit, refuse to post, or remove any materials submitted to or posted to its bulletin boards, guestbooks, story comments, or forums.Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in a public area online - for example, on message boards or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Norfolkdailynews.com is not responsible for the disclosure of your information under these circumstances and such disclosure is not covered under this privacy policy.Additionally, advertisers and vendors hosted on our site, or who link to our site, may collect information about you if you click on their ads, visit their Web sites, or make a purchase from them. Information collected by vendors or advertisers hosted on our site or who link to our site is not covered under this privacy policy.Finally, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.ChildrenNorfolkdailynews.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under the age of 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe norfolkdailynews.com has any information from or about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us at webmaster@norfolkdailynews.com.II. Disclosure to Third PartiesHow do I know my information is safe at Norfolkdailynews.com?In the normal course of business, Norfolkdailynews.com and Huse Publishing will not share your personal information with anyone. We will not license or rent our database of site visitor information to any outside entity. We collect this information for the sole purpose of improving Norfolkdailynews.com and providing more and better services to our guests.The only times we will divulge a guest's personal information to a third party are:· If we believe in good faith that the law requires such disclosure.· If we need to disclose the information in order to identify, contact or initiate legal action against someone violating Norfolkdailynews.com's Terms of Service, or someone who is causing injury to or interference with Norfolkdailynews.com's rights or property, other Norfolkdailynews.com users, or anyone else who can be harmed by such activities.· If Norfolkdailynews.com contracts with an outside research firm. In that case, we may provide information about you in order for the research firm to contact you regarding participating in surveys, focus groups or other research activities that will help us improve Norfolkdailynews.com's products and services. The research firm will be bound by its contract with Norfolkdailynews.com to use your information strictly for Norfolkdailynews.com research purposes, to keep your information confidential, and to adequately secure or destroy its records of your information when the research is complete so that information cannot be obtained by others.As described above, we and third parties may use cookies and other tracking technologies to facilitate serving relevant ads to you. For example, these technologies help us determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before, tailor ads to you if you have visited our site before, and avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. You can learn more about certain types of targeted advertising by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance website or Ad Choices site.In addition to disabling cookies and other tracking technologies as described above, you may opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from participating ad networks, audience segment providers, ad serving vendors, and other service providers by visiting websites operated by the Network Advertising Initiative and Digital Advertising Alliance.III. Use of User InformationHow Is My Information Used by Norfolkdailynews.com?Personal information collected from you at Norfolkdailynews.com, as well as information about traffic patterns and user behavior on the site, is used primarily for these purposes:· To conduct internal research. We constantly are assessing who is using our site and how they are using it. This assists us in making decisions about how to improve the site and to better serve our users. Research data are aggregated and do not include data about specific individuals. We may share aggregated research (but not individual user information) with our advertisers or business partners. Additionally, Norfolkdailynews.com may, at some time, use your personal information to contact you and ask if you would be willing to participate in a focus group, survey, or some other type of research effort.· To tailor advertising efforts. Most of the information and services available to you at Norfolkdailynews.com are free. In order to continue providing services free of charge, Norfolkdailynews.com sells advertising. Advertisers prefer to target their efforts toward audiences who are likely to be interested in their product. Your personal information helps us tell advertisers in general terms how many people are using our site and the demographic attributes of the people using different parts of our site. This helps the advertisers and Norfolkdailynews.com make a better decision about where to place advertising on the site. We never provide information about individual users to advertisers. However, if you choose to make a purchase from an advertiser on our site, that advertiser may collect personal information about you during the purchase process. Additionally, if you choose to purchase a classified advertisement that appears both on Norfolkdailynews.com and in the Norfolk Daily News, any information you provide during the purchase of that advertisement also will be provided to the Huse Publishing Company.More specifically, here is how Norfolkdailynews.com may use information you provide:· E-mail addresses. If you supply Norfolkdailynews.com with your e-mail address, either by registering on the site or by communicating with us via e-mail, we may, from time to time, send you information that we believe would be of interest to you via e-mail. This information may be from Norfolkdailynews.com, the Norfolk Daily News, or both.- Postal addresses. If you supply Norfolkdailynews.com with your postal address, we may send you periodic mailings with information on new products, coming events, surveys or other research materials, or other information we think might be of interest to you.· Telephone numbers. If you give us your telephone number, Norfolkdailynews.com may call you regarding orders you have placed online, or to tell you about new products or services, coming events, for research purposes, or to offer other information that may interest you.What if I don't want Norfolkdailynews.com to contact me?You can opt out of any or all personal contacts from Norfolkdailynews.com at any time. You may e-mail us at webmaster@norfolkdailynews.com You may also write or call us at the following address and phone number to notify us regarding use of your information:P.O. Box 977Norfolk NE 68702(402) 371-1020.If, sometime in the future, Norfolkdailynews.com decides to use your personal information in a way not described here, we will contact you beforehand to explain the use of the information and give you the opportunity to decline that use.Some Web sites collect user information and create lists or databases of this user information. These lists or databases are sometimes sold to third parties under contractual agreements that place limits on how the purchasing parties can reuse the information. Currently, Norfolkdailynews.com does NOT sell information about its users to third parties for any reason. If Norfolkdailynews.com chooses to do so in the future, we will notify you beforehand and give you the opportunity to tell us whether you want to participate.Cookies and how Norfolkdailynews.com uses themA cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred from a Web server through your browser and stored on the hard drive of your computer. The data in a cookie vary, depending on the reasons for the cookie. For example, if you have a special user name and password to log into a part of the Norfolkdailynews.com site, the cookie may contain your user name and password so that when you log on, the Web server recognizes you.Norfolkdailynews.com uses cookies to store visitor preferences, allow participation in polls and rating features, record session information, gather general information about its audience, store and measure traffic patterns on the site, and track information about you and the way you use the site.As Norfolkdailynews.com improves its service and offers its users more ability to customize their experience and the content they view, cookies may be used to assist in that personalization process.Advertisers on Norfolkdailynews.com may also use their own cookies. When you click on an advertisement, visit an advertiser's Web site or make a purchase from an advertiser, that company may use cookies according to their own policies. These uses of cookies are not covered under Norfolkdailynews.com's policy.You do not have to permit the use of cookies. You can, through the options in your Web browser, choose to accept all cookies, choose to reject all cookies or choose to receive notification when a cookie is being delivered so that you can make a decision whether to accept each cookie on a case-by-case basis. If you refuse all cookies, or refuse particular cookies, you will not be able to use some of the features of Norfolkdailynews.com, including, but not limited to, opinion polls and personalized or customized features.IV. Security of InformationSecurity technologiesNorfolkdailynews.com uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. When we transfer or receive certain types of sensitive information, such as financial information, we will redirect you to a secure server. We also have appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you.V. Accuracy of User InformationMaking corrections to your personal informationUpon request, you can check on all information that we maintain about you, including unique identifier information, contact information (name, address, phone number, e-mail), and any other information we maintain about you.You can also request that inaccuracies be corrected in your contact information, financial information, unique identifiers, or any other information that we maintain.Submit your request by contacting Norfolkdailynews.com via e-mail, postal mail, or telephone.Contacting Norfolkdailynews.comIf you have any questions about our privacy policy or the privacy practices of this site, please contact us at webmaster@norfolkdailynews.comYou may telephone us at (402) 371-1020. You may also write to us at:Norfolkdailynews.comP.O. Box 977Norfolk NE, 68701VI. Membership and RegistrationMiscellaneousNorfolkdailynews.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time in its discretion and to notify users of any such changes solely by changing this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of Norfolkdailynews.com after the posting of any amended Privacy Policy shall constitute your agreement to be bound by any such changes. Your use of this site prior to the time this Privacy Policy was posted will be governed according to the Privacy Policy that applied at the time of your use.Norfolkdailynews.com may modify, suspend, discontinue or restrict the use of any portion of Norfolkdailynews.com, including the availability of any portion of the content at any time, without notice or liability. Norfolkdailynews.com may deny access to any person or user at any time for any reason.
